[music]
>> And thank you Trent.
>> cool. Thank you Trent for the new intro.
You're watching the DMZ America podcast
with editorial cartoonist Ted Rall. I'm
Ted Rall I'm coming from the left and
coming from the right is Oh, I don't
know if I could do that anymore
awkwardly. I'm Scott Stantis right
coming you cartoon man. I'll eat you.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay.
Thanks so much.
Joining us for the hour is John
Kiriakou, my co-host on the program with
Ted Rall and John Kiriakou. This is your
first visit over to the DMZ world. Thank
you so much for joining us. Thanks for
having me. John Kiriakou is of course
the noted CIA whistleblower.
I can't imagine there's a lot of people
here on DMZ who don't know who you are.
So
I don't think we need to go that much
more into that. Not to mention
John, you're like Tik Tok famous. You
have like over a billion views and it's
kind of like if nobody knows who if you
don't know who John Kiriakou is, climb
out from your rock and you know.
Yeah, crazy.
>> Get turned on the internet. It's crazy.
So
Scott,
just the other day
like last week you and I were talking
about something and you were like oh,
can you ask John and I thought you know
what? We could just ask I don't need to
be
>> [laughter]
>> the in between person here. We can have
we can have you guys have John come on
and we can talk about it. So
thanks John for joining us and um
Scott you have questions. John has
questions.
>> have I was I was thinking about this
this episode where I was trying to think
do I start with the little stuff and you
know, climb up or do I hit the big
question first and dig down. So I'm
going to start with the big question and
dig down John. And again, thank you so
much for joining us. I really appreciate
it.
>> it's a pleasure. I'm very happy to meet
you. I've reached I've read it I've read
Oh my god, I'm I've got Ted-itis all of
a sudden.
>> [laughter]
>> I've been
watching a lot of your videos over the
last week.
Fascinating stuff and
it kind of harkens back for me the you
may be a little younger than me but do
you remember the Frank Church hearings
from the 70s looking into the CIA
activities and the shenanigans as Chef
we say. Um
in watching and listening to what you
were talking about and all the cases you
just you you you you described. Um
everything from the kill lists to the
different um
I I I guess the question is
and it's really simple but it's very
big. Is it is it worth it? Should we
have this big of an intelligence
operation going? Um
I mean here's an example if I could and
there will be a point. I swear.
>> [laughter]
>> Um I was I was on a podcast in Chicago
and at the end of the podcast there was
five of us and uh media types and at the
end of the podcast we were asked for
your recommendation of the week. And you
know, I'd say nine times out of 10 all
of us absolutely forgot we were doing
that segment and you're just and then
you're going you're scrambling like hell
in your head
>> [laughter]
>> trying to think what
And does that that does that kind of
thing happen like with the kill list? I
have to believe it's every Tuesday,
right? There's some meeting and they put
together this list. And do do do a lot
of those people show up at the meeting
and just go God, oh shoot. I didn't do
the work.
There's a Botswanan rapper I don't like.
Yeah, name him.
Put him on the list. Not necessarily
among those choosing the targets.
But among the the army of lawyers that
comes to these
or came to these meetings, I would say
yeah. I think that's exactly what
happens. So you've got this staff in the
CIA's counterterrorism center.
Mostly young analysts
and their job is to come up with a list
of the most dangerous people in the
world that week, right? Who who presents
and this is one of the legal
qualifications
a clear and present danger to the United
States, to American citizens or American
installations. And you come up with the
list. These are the clear and present
danger people.
And then you turn it over to the
lawyers. So you've got
lawyers from the CIA's General Counsel's
office, the lawyer from the CIA's
Counterterrorism Center, the lawyer from
the Office of Legal Counsel at the
Justice Department, the lawyer from the
White House Counsel's office. In in the
case of
John Brennan during the Obama
presidency, it was
the White House Counsel Kathryn Remler
whom we now know because she is so
prominent in the Epstein files, her dear
and abiding friend Jeffrey Epstein.
And [snorts] um
and then the lawyers from the National
Security Council.
So the lawyers like
grossly outweigh
the operators and the operators just got
the list from the analysts who say oh, I
follow this thing and this guy Ahmed
Schmahmad is very very dangerous. We
should kill him.
And then that's what they do.
God, that's amazing. But I guess and the
bigger question I'll come back to it is
so many operations. I mean what was it
what was it Ted about two a year or two
years ago American soldier killed in
Niger.
And you're going
what?
It's sort of like saying, you know,
Elizabeth Eskimo not Mogadishu. It's
like it doesn't it didn't compute. Why
were we in Niger and why was an American
soldier there? The intelligence
apparatus is so vast now and from your
description particularly and so
overarching and just I keep coming back
to
why do we need do we need something that
big John?
No.
Absolutely not. And if and if anything,
it's counterproductive. It gets us into
more and more trouble all the time.
Uh for example
you mentioned Niger and this and this
Sahel.
It's it's one of the most dangerous
places on Earth now.
Um
but in great part because of us.
Because we decided well, the French have
just up and moved out and they've just
you know, walked away from these
countries. That means that we have to go
in and [snorts] and fill the vacuum
because this is a mess.
>> Yeah, right. What could possibly go
wrong, right? You know, there's this
Al-Qaeda this nascent Al-Qaeda movement
and they're allied with Boko Haram and
then there are elements of ISIS. So
we're going to go in and we're going to
make things right. And instead we go in
knowing nothing about the region,
knowing nothing about the culture
without the the relationships necessary
to allow these operations to succeed in
the first place and we get our asses
kicked. And then we see these little
blurbs in the Washington Post that a
soldier was killed during a training
accident
in Africa.
What's that code for? Yeah, exactly.
It's code for somebody launched an
operation against us and killed a bunch
of special forces guys. And then
whenever they say civilian
employee of the Pentagon that's code for
a CIA officer.
Well, let's assume for a moment you're
appointed head of the CIA.
Or even
is there
a more
is there a larger umbrella that controls
all intelligence? Um Yeah, DNI.
Okay, so you're you're you're DNI
director. What do you do?
What what are your first what are your
first moves?
DNI director is actually less powerful
than the CIA director. Well, let's make
you CIA director. Okay. Um
I'm a little bit biased because I've had
something of a bad experience with the
CIA over the last
>> [laughter]
>> I heard something about that.
So grouchy, John. Yeah,
>> [laughter]
>> got a few years in jail. Let it go, man.
You know, I used to work for a guy named
Jim Pavitt. Jim was the Deputy Director
for Operations. And Jim had this mantra.
He would just repeat it like almost
every day in our morning meeting.
The job of the CIA is to recruit spies,
to steal secrets and to analyze those
secrets so that the president can make
the best informed policy.
He would say it every day. It's not to
it's not to be in charge of these
multi-billion dollar satellites that can
do something that's slightly better than
what it could do five years ago. It
wasn't to negotiate with Eric Prince to
get some mercenary army into some
godforsaken place. It was to recruit
spies, to steal secrets. And if there is
going to be a CIA, I'm not convinced
that we need one anymore.
Um or even that we ever did. Um in fact,
Harry Truman once said that he was a
damn fool for creating the CIA in the
first place.
Yeah, why did he say that?
Because he believed that the CIA had
killed John Kennedy.
Yeah, he wrote an op-ed in the
Washington Post
a few days after Kennedy was
assassinated in which he sort of cast
shadow on the CIA and the Post ran the
article in its morning edition and then
pulled it in the afternoon edition.
Yeah, I was going to say that's I've not
heard that that's explosive. That's
Yeah, so I you know,
listen, I'm a realist. I know we can't
do away with the CIA. It would take an
act of Congress that would never ever
ever happen. And so I would do my best
to get the CIA out of the business
of counterterrorism, turn that over to
the Pentagon, let them deal with it. Um
and
and at the CIA, I would bring it back to
the basics of recruiting spies to steal
secrets.
Can I a bit of a sea change here but I
know I'm asking this for Ted, myself and
the entire dying profession.
Um what is the world view of cartoonists
and cartoon editorial cartooning? Does
it I mean it seems to have had some some
some power, but I mean that's been
>> Very dangerous. These cartoonists they
want us to take [laughter] them lightly.
They're very dangerous these guys.
Um in all seriousness, uh
the power of political cartooning is not
lost on the world's leaders.
They worry about political cartoonists.
Which is stunning to me why the United
States and why
we've gone over this topic a million
times on this podcast, but it just it's
still infuriating that editors in the
United States
have always hated us, always. I mean
I've been a staff cartoonist for 45
years. And you know, oh go do your
little cartoons. And can I share a quick
story with you? You're going to love
this. Um this is inside information. I
mean I can talk about it cuz I don't
work for them anymore.
Um I was working at the Birmingham News
here in Birmingham, Alabama.
And they decided to do an actual
scientific study. They had focus groups
as part of this this program. And one
day was focused or one morning was
focused on editorial pages. And so they
had sat down the 10 15 people, however
many it was. They said, "How do you you
know,
so do you read the editorial page? How
many of you read the editorial page
every day?" All the hands go up. "How
many of you read the cartoon?" All the
hands go up. "How many of you read the
editorials?" Two hands go up. "How many
of you read the columns?" Like three
hands go up. "How many of you read the
letters?" Four three or four hands go
up. And they said
and then they started the question. You
can see where this is going. They
started asking questions of these of the
focus group. "What you know, what do you
read?" I said, "Oh well, what do you
like about the editorials?" I said,
"Well, we don't. We like the cartoon."
"Well, what do you like about the
columns?" "Well, we don't. We like the
cartoons."
John, I'm not making this up. The next
group that came in, they had blacked out
my cartoons.
>> [laughter]
>> So so so so they had to focus on the you
know, the wretched editorials and the
you know, and then on the other hand
Time will tell.
>> [laughter]
>> You know,
it's I think it's because you guys can
say something
that's so powerful
it actually becomes more powerful than
anything that a that a
written journalist could say
and get away with it. You know, for
example, a couple things that come to
mind.
I remember
Garry Trudeau doing whatever it was,
four panels, three panels, whatever it
was.
Four. And it was Frank Sinatra singing
My Way, right? So here's Sinatra on
stage holding the mic and he's singing
the the words to My Way. Same thing in
the second panel. Same thing in the
third panel. And then the fourth panel
was an actual photograph.
And it says, "Frank Sinatra doing it his
way with
Joe Gaspipe Casso,
uh
Jimmy the Jimmy the Weasel, you know,
this guy,
uh
Frank uh
the Killer, this guy." And it was all
these like bosses and underbosses of the
five families.
But it's not like a a reporter said,
"Frank Sinatra's in the mafia."
You don't have to say Frank Sinatra's in
the mafia. All you had to do was show
that picture and then handwrite in Garry
Trudeau's, you know, recognizable
handwriting, handwrite the names of the
people that Frank Sinatra's, you know,
yucking it up with.
It it's hard for journalists to to be
able written journalists to be able to
do something like that and I think that
they just don't have the power that
editorial cartoonists have.
Well, to the portrayal
Ted's a good example of portrayal of
George President George W. Bush as just
sort of a you know, runny nose [__]
Right.
>> Um you know, clearly he wasn't either of
those, you know,
obviously, but the portrayal of that is
incre I mean I'm looking at Herblock
having Nixon coming out of the sewer,
you know, "Hey everyone, the vice
president's here."
Um you know,
>> [laughter]
>> Oliphant's portrayal of um of Jimmy
Carter and just becoming smaller and
smaller and smaller along with Jeff
MacNelly did the same thing. I mean they
defined those presidencies.
And I I I'm just consistently shocked.
And so when you hear about other
cartoonists in other countries, they're
the ones who are really getting, you
know, uh bombarded by oppressive
regimes. And so they don't have to do
that here. They newspaper business
pretty much killed us. And it's
I I just obviously, okay. You you I
touched my own nerve. That was
>> [laughter]
>> It's Hearing Ted's story from the LA
Times, I mean it's it's it gives you a
knot in your stomach that something like
that could happen in 21st century
America. But it does.
Well, and doing cartoons that are
clearly like, you know, you you drew
the cartoonist who had worked at the uh
Chicago Tribune prior to me, a guy named
Dick Locher. Great guy.
Pulitzer Prize winning cartoonist. But
he drew Netanyahu and they got tons of
complaints and he had to the paper
apologized because he drew Netanyahu
because he looked Jewish.
I'm going, "Folks,
>> [laughter]
>> look at the flag.
What's on it?" And it wasn't like an
overt like like, you know, something
from the Nazi Right. Like the 30s.
Yeah. Yeah, it wasn't it wasn't anything
close to that, but they also were afraid
that we get attacked so consistent so so
consistently and furiously and Ted can
attest to this as well for just, you
know,
people say, "Well, this cartoon you did
you said this." I go, "Well, that's not
what where I was going." And they said,
"I know where you were going." You're
going
Okay. [sighs]
Okay, first wife. It's like, okay.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, exactly.
You know what I'm thinking. That's an
amazing skill set you have. That's a
remarkable Yeah. Um I wish you knew what
the stock market were thinking. That
that would be more useful.
Well, talking I mean
Tucker Carlson's I I do want to ask you
about the Tucker Carlson thing. Is he is
this just all [__] I'm sorry. I'm
I'm hearing him say that the CIA is
putting together an I you know, uh
a case to arrest him for I guess
sedition or being a traitor.
>> that's not how the system works.
Okay.
>> Um
Almost every morning
one of the deputy director's briefers
would say there was a leak in the New
York Times today. There was a leak in
the Washington Post today. There was a
leak in the Wall Street Journal today.
And he would report on what the leak was
and the deputy director would say,
"Okay, send over a crimes report." A
crimes report is a memo from the CIA to
the Justice Department saying there was
a leak in the paper today. This is what
the leak said. This is why it's
classified.
99 times out of a hundred times
they just file it.
One time out of a hundred, maybe they'll
start doing an investigation.
So number one
we now know that that the
allegation, the ridiculous allegation,
assertion that Tucker Carlson was
somehow working for the Iranians did not
come from the CIA.
It came from Laura Loomer
who is one of the most radical
crazy people
who is
on the political scene these days. She's
a nut.
And um and I'm happy to say that
publicly. She This is a woman who's
banned for life from Uber, Lyft, and
Target because she because of her
anti-Arab, anti-Muslim hate speech. And
um
and you know, insistence that people
become violent against Muslims and
Arabs. Okay. So Laura Loomer came out on
Sunday and said, "It was me. I did it. I
did it. I wrote a letter to the Justice
Department and I said that Tucker
Carlson is a paid agent of the Iranian
government and he should be arrested for
treason." Well, of course treason is
constitutionally defined. People throw
around that word like it has no real
meaning. It has very specific meaning.
And in almost every case it carries with
it the death penalty. Mhm.
So
Laura Loomer said without any evidence
at all, just because she doesn't like
what Tucker Carlson is saying, said that
Tucker Carlson is a paid agent of the
Iranian government. And so even if he
were, because he does not have access to
classified information, that would make
him guilty of violating FARA, the
foreign agents registration act, which
means failing to fill out an internet
form. Mhm.
>> Right? So the the penalty
uh for a first offense, I I looked this
up actually. I've written an op-ed about
it. The penalty for a first offense, um
the guideline is zero to six months in
the local jail. Okay. First of all, he's
not a paid agent of the Iranian
government.
He has plenty of money. In addition to
making, you know, eight figures a year
himself,
his his step-grandfather
was named Swanson and was the inventor
of Swanson frozen foods. He pioneered
frozen foods.
The TV dinner was created by Tucker
Carlson's family. They're rich beyond
their wildest dreams. He doesn't need
Iranian money. He's not taking Iranian
money. It's ridiculous.
Um
but furthermore
even if he was taking Iranian money
zero to six months is not exactly the
death penalty, is it?
So uh this is just Laura Loomer trying
desperately to remain
to remain
relevant in conservative circles. She's
not in most conservative circles because
she's a nut and she's a bigot and um and
she's nothing but trouble. You know, she
ran for Congress back in I think it was
2018. In the district that includes
Mar-a-Lago and and Palm Beach. And she
got like 23%. Nobody wants her. Nobody
likes her. Nobody pays any attention to
her. She's not smart enough to have her
own show on Fox or Newsmax or anywhere
else.
And so she just throws a grenade into
the middle of the room every once in a
while just to see what happens.
I have to congratulate you by the way
on one of the podcasts you were asked
about why you were working for at the
time it was
Sputnik.
And your response was exactly what mine
I was a regular guest on Ted's show and
people would when we when Ted got tons
of crap as much as you did and I got
some you know No doubt. second hand
crap.
>> [laughter]
>> And
but I loved your answer. I just like
because why why are you working why you
working for Sputnik? Why are you
talking? Because they're the only ones
who asked.
Yeah, my variant on that was it's not
like CNN is burning up my phone line.
Yeah, Fox News never calls.
It's it's amazing how people who you
know they they get upset that you take a
gig and they don't want to offer you a
gig. They don't care if you die under a
bridge out in the cold and in the rain.
They they're just like just don't do
that. It's like okay well as like as
long as you know Russia or whoever Press
TV which is Iran. Anyway, as long as
they're not telling me what to say or
what to do
I'll talk to anybody. You know and I'll
add one thing to that too.
CNN doesn't call me anymore.
MSNBC stopped calling me years ago. Did
they?
Fox I'm on Fox all the time.
Um but usually cuz they want me to take
a swipe at the CIA or to explain
something that the CIA is doing. I never
ever say no. Never.
Because they're the only ones that ask.
Now with that said the very first time I
ever went on Fox it was on Fox and
Friends in the morning.
And they said we're going to send you
over the questions so that you're
prepared. I said great thanks. So they
send me the questions. As I'm reading
through the questions I get a second
email from them and it says suggested
responses. OH.
NO. And I was like
oh no you don't. Absolutely not. And I
ignored it.
Oh wow. They only did that once and that
was
oh I'm talking now 15 years ago.
No way. Yeah, suggested responses.
In case what you're not smart enough to
answer her question. I kind of like it.
>> [laughter]
>> You know one thing that the networks do
all all the networks do this. It drives
me crazy too. They'll say hey can you
come on tonight and talk about X Y and Z
and I always say sure.
And then they say well we just need to
do a quick pre-interview. So what's your
opinion on this question? And you tell
them your opinion and they're like okay
I'll call you right back. And then they
call back a minute later and they say
you know what we decided to go a
different way on this story.
>> [laughter]
>> We won't need you tonight. That happens
to me a lot. Yeah. Yeah, that's happened
to me a few times as well. That's
>> [laughter]
>> So when they when they say the media is
skewed or it's yeah that it is. Just
just for those you kids out there who
still have dreams and hopes. I mean I
love the inside stuff is so fun. I mean
there was the time I was on with Sean
Hannity and he was reaming me over
you know Reagan had just died and I
sorry Scott I know you liked President
But I but I said I had just issued
something and said oh yeah I'm sure he's
turning crispy brown by now.
Hannity Hannity goes well you know what
do you have against Reagan? And so I
mentioned a bunch of stuff and I said oh
you know and he killed Gaddafi's
daughter
just for fun basically. And he said well
that's because of the
the the disco bombing. That's that was
in retaliation for that and I said oh
you know and I was like well I have a
gotcha moment here. I was like well
that's interesting Reagan must have
totally had clairvoyance because that he
killed that girl years before the disco
bombing.
And
I hear I could hear the buzzing the
producer yelling in his ear go to break
go to break.
>> [laughter]
>> AND THEN YEAH TED WE'RE NOT GOOD WE'RE
DONE HERE. YEAH, we're not going to need
you. Or launch into Ronald Ronald Reagan
time traveler.
>> [laughter]
>> The the last time I was on MSNBC was
2016.
I was on with Dan Ellsberg.
And what was the guy's name Ari was it
Ari Melber? Is that his name? He was on
MSNBC. I can't remember. I think it was
Ari Melber or was he at CNN? I can't
remember. I think I think he's yeah I
think he's MSNBC.
Yeah. So
they they called me earlier in the day
they said we're going to have you split
screen with Daniel Ellsberg. I said oh
my god Dan's one of my favorite people.
He's a mentor to me. We've been friends
for years. It'll be great.
So um
they said it's going to be on I forget
what the issue was. I said fantastic
whistleblowing. How would you like to be
addressed?
And I said or identified. I said either
CIA torture whistleblower John Kiriakou
CIA former CIA officer John Kiriakou
former CIA counterterrorism officer John
Kiriakou. I said whatever you guys
prefer that either any of those three.
They said okay.
So I go all the freaking way up Nebraska
Avenue.
MSNBC and NBC are not close to anything
right? So I go all the way up to the end
of Nebraska Avenue. I'm almost in
Maryland.
And it's like an armed camp. You have to
be buzzed into the compound. It's got
barbed wire.
It's ridiculous. So I go in
heavy makeup even heavier than Fox which
struck me as odd. And and then I get
wired up. So I'm sitting there
and um
and they put Dan on the screen. I said
hi Dan. He says hi John. How are you? I
say great to see you Dan. And then Ari
Melber comes on and he's like okay so
here's what we're going to do. I'm going
to have the first question to Dan and
the second question to John and it's
going to be about whistleblowing. I said
great. So he starts off
um
uh whistleblower
Daniel Ellsberg told us about the
Pentagon Papers which concluded that the
US is losing the war in Vietnam and Dan
answers his question. And then he says
and now we go to convicted felon John
Kiriakou.
And I go [__]
I said like that loud. On air.
[__] I said we went over this
with your [__] producers.
And he's like so I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm
sorry. I said I'm I'm done. I'm walking
out. I stood up and I start taking this
stuff off me you know the the
microphones and stuff. He's like please
please I'm sorry. That was my [__] up.
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry. We'll start
back at the beginning again.
And I said don't ever [__] set me up
like that again I told him. Don't ever
do that again. So I did the interview.
They never called me again.
Wasn't it taped? Was it a taper or was
it live? It was taped. It was like four
hours before it was
>> [clears throat]
>> yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, I had I had you know well
>> [snorts]
>> Hannity
you know so they they the producer calls
you and usually tells you exactly what
the subject is going to be.
Gary Trudeau of Doonesbury had done a
controversial cartoon. I was the
president of the AAEC which is the
editorial cartoonists association and
they said oh can you come in and share
your expertise about editorial about
political cartooning. I said and I knew
Sean Hannity and I was like all right so
this is not about my cartooning. This is
only about
Gary Trudeau and Doonesbury and about
cartooning in general. Correct. I'm like
this is not going to involve any
controversial cartoon of mine.
Right.
So
I go on and of course we never even talk
about Trudeau. He immediately pops up of
like a two-year-old controversial
cartoon I'd done of mine.
I was I wanted to throw a chair at him.
You know I I I think I would have become
a Geraldo-like hero to to all liberals
everywhere. But I was so furious. But we
were live.
I was just like your I go I'm like your
producer lied to me. He goes oh like we
don't lie. We don't make deals. I'm like
yeah you do. And so we got into a big
shouting match and I never went back.
That happened to me on NPR. And it's the
last time I was on NPR. As I was walking
out I said to the producer don't ever
call me again. And they haven't. But
yeah please come on Saturday morning.
It's going to be great. We're going to
talk about Gina Haspel. I'd just written
this op-ed in the Washington Post about
Gina Haspel.
Being you know the mother of the torture
program. And
and so I go on and it's this guy was it
Stevinsky? He has he has spinal stenosis
so he can't sit. Stevinsky. So he's
standing the whole time. And
so I'm looking up at him which was
weird. I mean nobody would know that cuz
it's radio anyway but but it was weird.
So as soon as we go on the air and it's
live he attacks.
And um Wow. Yeah.
He attacked my piece and said that
ProPublica had written an article based
on my piece and then they they retracted
one of the sentences and like don't you
do any due diligence? And I said I
published in the post what the CIA
permitted me to publish in the post. I'm
not the fact checker for the Washington
Post or for ProPublica.
And he just kept coming in. So I went
right back at him. And where were you?
Where were you when I was blowing the
whistle on the torture program? Because
I don't remember NPR saying anything
about it. I don't remember NPR calling
the CIA to task or the Bush
administration to task. I said, "Where
were you when I was arrested? What about
the other eight whistleblowers arrested
during the Obama administration? Where
was NPR? Nowhere to be found."
And then I got up I walked out. It was
supposed to be the whole half hour. I
was in there 5 minutes. I got up. I
said, "Don't ever call me again." And I
walked out. You were right. I I
embarrassed them. And then as soon as I
walked out of the building, my phone
just blew up. I didn't realize it. Like
all of my friends and acquaintances
listen to NPR on Saturday mornings. Of
course.
>> "Oh my god, you gave it to him. It was
incredible. Good for you."
>> [laughter]
>> I said, "I guarantee you I'll never be
called by NPR ever again." And I haven't
been. No. Well, NPR is you know, NPR Let
me just add my story. Um
this is how Ted and I actually became
friends. I was president of the
Association of American Editorial
Cartoonists. And Ted, this will surprise
you John, did a controversial cartoon
>> [laughter]
>> making fun of terror widows. Um and look
it up. It's actually an excellent
cartoon in hindsight. He was actually
right, but it was it seemed pretty raw
at the time. So Alan Keyes, remember
him? Uh was on um it was I had to I had
to Was that Fox or God, I can't remember
if that was Fox or CNN. But they asked
me to come on as the president of the
cartoons association. I tried to be
nuanced. Not
>> [laughter]
>> Not the right Always a good idea.
Because I started to say, "While I don't
agree with what Ted drew, he has And
Alan had Congressman King from Long
Island. I can't remember
>> I remember him too. He was another
troublemaker.
>> What an [__]
What a dick. Because all they did was I
could not finish
>> [clears throat]
>> my highly nuanced explanation. I said,
"While I didn't agree with what Ted And
that's all I had to say." And they WERE
JUST LIKE
AND IF YOU
I went back and looked at the
transcripts because they post back then
they posted the transcripts on the show.
And there are whole blocks that say
indecipherable. Indecipherable.
[laughter] All three of us were yelling
at each other. It was the worst
television you could possibly It would
have been worse radio. Um because they
just started screaming at me and started
telling that Ted should be arrested,
should be thrown in jail.
Um Alan Keyes said on that show and and
wrote very clearly, decipherably in a
column, that I should be shot. Yes.
>> He he alluded to that as well. Well,
that that afternoon, [laughter]
I get a phone call from one Ted Rall,
who I didn't know very well at the time.
And [laughter] you just gave me so much
crap for doing such a shitty job. And I
actually responded and said, "Yeah,
you're absolutely right. I wasn't I you
know, I I came in with my chin up and an
apology, which was a stupid It should
have just been, you know, anyone who
thinks that he can't doesn't have a
right to say this is you know, should be
should leave the country, you know.
>> Yeah, yeah, you don't get into that
whole like when you're you know, you're
there to defend you're just there there
to defend free speech. Like what I think
is neither here nor there, right? Like
this is like and you defend the cartoon
and and the cartoonist. You just say
like
>> Yes.
I did. And Ted to his
Yeah. Ted to his credit forgave me.
>> [laughter]
>> For my
>> Yeah, but also he apologized and you
know, I melt when it comes to an
apology, you know? Like if
if that [__] Austin Beutner ever
picked up the phone and called me,
former the guy who [__] me at the LA
Times, and said, "You know, I'm really
[__] sorry. Let's sit down and talk
about it." I would melt. I would. I mean
cuz nobody ever does that.
Which is weird.
>> One of the guys who was responsible for
putting me in prison, like directly one
of one of three people directly
responsible for putting me in prison,
called me. I was out of prison for a
couple of weeks and he called me and he
said he wanted to apologize. It's been
bothering him since I first got in
trouble. And And he invited me for
coffee. And I said, "Of course." And I
met him at a hotel. He apologized
profusely. We had coffee. And I never
saw him again, which is perfectly fine.
I accepted his apology. That's all I
wanted. We don't have to be pals or
anything. We don't have to go out
together and hang out. But it's hard to
apologize sometimes. And And he did. He
made the effort.
Yeah, you can't go back in time. I'm not
expecting that.
>> Yep. So
So let me ask you John, how are you
handling um dealing with internet fame?
I mean as Ted mentioned at the top of
the show, a billion downloads of all
your videos. No, I mean seriously, you
actually took a you took a tact that I
really respect. And that is you went on
every podcast when everyone was like,
"Oh, it's a podcast about some [__]
in his basement. Blah blah blah." I even
did a high school kids podcast. Did you
really? See, I think it's
Trump did that in uh '16. He did in '20.
He did in '24. He was on every
>> Yeah, but how did that work out? Oh,
wait. Yeah. And well, Kamala refused to
be on like Rogan wanted her on. And he
she she's like, "Well, she can only come
on for half an hour. And we need to know
the questions." Well, [__] you. It's
right. You're You're asking to be
president of the
>> Maybe she needed the suggested She
needed the list of suggested answers.
>> Suggested responses. Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> Unbelievable. But how are you dealing
with it? That's got to be I mean
seriously, you because now I have to
believe you walk through public and
people recognize you. You're
recognizable.
>> Constantly.
And how are you handling that?
Are you I mean you are you enjoying it?
Is it a pain in the ass? No, I I I
embrace it. People are so nice. It's
incredible. They relate to me, but
there's one like theme that runs through
this. Like that they like they like the
stories. They They like the way this Gen
Z kid like made lasers shoot out of my
eyes and made give me the Alvin and the
Chipmunks voice. That's all fun and
games, but there's this theme that runs
through it. And that is that they
respect me for telling the truth. Mhm.
And so that's what I've clung to.
Um I I rather enjoy being recognized.
And it's not just, you know, walking
down the street in DC. I told Ted
earlier this morning,
I found myself kind of lost and
disoriented yesterday in in the Hanover,
Germany uh uh
train station.
And this kid runs up to me, a Lebanese
refugee. He's like, "I watch you and Ted
every day. Oh, wow.
>> news from you and Ted.
What What What can I help you do? You
need to find the right train tracks?"
I'm like, "Yeah, I don't know where the
heck I'm going. I don't speak German and
everything's in German." So he he helped
me. That happens every day. I was in
Kuwait a month ago or so, a month and a
half ago. I walk out. I get I did a
podcast. I walk out of the building and
this guy stops,
looks at me, and he's like, "John, are
you John?" And I said, "Yes."
He says, "I'm Ali Reza from North
Macedonia.
I listen to you every day." I'm like,
"In North Macedonia?" He's [laughter]
like, "Yes. I'm Albanian. I used to
listen to you in Albania."
It's like, "Great. Awesome." So I feel
like I'm having an impact, but it's only
since things went viral about 3 weeks
ago
that I realized
how much of an impact and how it's it's
global, really. I I've even been hired
by
members of two different royal families
to consult for them
because of what I did.
You know,
ethics in their own intelligence
operations.
So things have really seriously turned
around. And we talked about apologies a
moment ago.
I got a I got an email through eBay.
Right? You know how
if you're if you're a seller on eBay or
a buyer, you have an account and people
can message you through eBay. So I get a
message through eBay, "Is this John
Kiriakou, the whistleblower?" Wow.
>> And I said, "Yes, it is." And he says,
long long email from this guy. He's
like, "I'm one of the FBI agents who
arrested you. And I've had trouble
sleeping ever since we did it. He said,
"I want you to know how ashamed I am for
what I did. We were ordered by people at
the very top of the food chain to do
this to you."
You know, on and on and on about how
sorry he is. He's no longer at the FBI.
He's the third FBI agent to apologize.
>> And that is how it worked. That's
totally how it worked. It was not their
idea. They were ordered to do it.
>> don't I don't blame you guys.
I know exactly how this happened. I know
John Brennan did this to me and Eric
Holder. They were the ones that did this
to me. I don't blame you guys.
But yeah, I mean it sucks. Now that I'm
sort of recognized as this truth teller,
I feel like I've I've come full circle.
And then people are looking back on 2012
thinking, "Oh, that that stuff should
never have happened to him."
Oh, well, there's no question. I mean
anyone
any rational person. Thank you. But
that's becoming fewer and fewer of us,
but no, that should never have happened
for crying out loud. What happens next?
What do you I mean I know uh you have a
weekend show on RT. Is that correct?
Yeah, I have a weekend show on RT. Uh
they just changed the name to Deep
State, The Deep State or I think it's
just Deep State. Everything's You're all
You're all into alliteration with D's,
right? Yeah, it's not working
out.
>> Yeah.
>> Just don't be Deep Six.
I Disco Hour. God forbid. Um but it
because of It started with Rogan and
then ending with the
virality of of these clips, um I was
signed by the Creative Artists Agency,
CAA. And they're going to represent me
now in everything.
>> Congratulations. It is in books and and
Hollywood and consulting and licensing.
I'm getting a lot of advertising pitches
now. Really? Can I ask what? Cuz I'd
just be curious what
Um today I got like six.
Three of them were for different
pharmaceuticals of all things. Um one
was for a a vineyard. Um uh one was for
men's clothing line. And one was uh
Parker Warby Parker.
That's your second glasses one. My
second glasses one cuz I wear Tom Ford
frames. I just happened to like choose
the Tom Ford frames. And somebody from
Tom Ford recognized them as Tom Ford
frames. So do I want to do a print
layout for Tom Ford? I said absolutely
yes.
That's awesome. That is so fun. How does
that work? Do you have to uh Kim like if
you do glass Can if you do Tom Ford, can
you not do Warby Parker or vice versa?
>> Correct. Yeah.
>> Yeah, I would imagine there's an
exclusivity. The other thing though is
what's I'm just trying to think of the
ad campaign. It's like, you know,
what's my secret?
>> [laughter]
>> Well, I'll tell you what.
I started doing um Cameos a couple of
weeks ago.
>> Yeah, I Ted told me. And they're going
just gangbusters. Like I've actually set
a record for the number of Cameos um
that any one person has done. I I've
defeated George Santos. I'm now the
Cameo King.
>> [laughter]
>> Um Don, you're making me feel so
inferior. John
referred me to Cameo.
Um zero requests. Zero.
>> It's coming. It's coming.
So um John has to get up early in the
morning to do them.
>> I do. I actually set my alarm 5:00 in
the morning to get up and try to catch
up on the Cameos. Like right now
I have
88 in queue.
Yeah. Wow.
>> got to get done. So it's got to be done
before
the the CEO of Cameo is flying to DC to
have lunch with me next week.
Wow. It's the craziest thing. You're the
Are you the number one biggest person on
Cameo in of all time?
I I'm I'm going to be the number one of
all time soon. Another week or two of
this, yeah. I'm the only person who's
who's made like a There's a certain like
threshold of money every day for five
consecutive days.
Nobody else has done it in the history
of Cameo. The people who who ask you to
do the Cameo, do they write the copy for
you or um is there any copy that you
>> Sometimes.
Is there any copy that you won't do?
Yeah. There are a couple things that I
I've said no to.
Like one one guy wanted me to endorse
his meme coin. And I'm like, absolutely
not. I have enough trouble in my life. I
don't need the SEC on my on my back on
top of it. So no, I'm not doing that.
Um and then a couple people Like some of
them are really cute. Like this 11th
grader asked me if I would endorse him
for junior class president at Granada
Hills High School in California. I said
absolutely.
So most of the time
>> What if he What if he's a What if
[laughter] he's a little shitty kid?
And he's And you endorsed the wrong kid
for that important race.
Hey, man.
>> [laughter]
>> His His $198 did the talking.
I mean, are you so You meant You touched
on the legal troubles. Are your legal
troubles over now? Are you still
wrestling with some residual [__]
You know, knock on wood, Scott.
I was I was wrestling with residual
[__] until a week ago. Wow. A week
ago. And I was able to finally get it
all behind me. After all these years,
it's been 14 years plus. 14 years and 2
months. Finally got it behind me.
Ugh. Yeah. Ugh. I'm so sorry. That just
I mean
>> Thank you. But you know what though? I I
can't help but to think that that this
was just, you know,
if you believe in God, this was the
plan, the test. If you believe in fate,
this was what I was fated to to do. It
It's just This is just the way it is.
And so I I have to embrace it. There was
a person with whom I was once very close
and with whom I share three children. Um
who I'm forbidden from mentioning by
court order. Who once gave me really
really wonderful advice.
She said,
this is right after my arrest. She said,
you have to embrace this. You can't hide
from it. Mhm. You have to embrace it.
And you have to keep telling your side
of the story over and over and over
again because eventually they're going
to move on to their next victim. And
they did. It was Ed Snowden.
If you keep telling your story, your
side is going to be the side of record.
And she was right. And then even my
brother said to me once, days after my
arrest,
he said, I know you can't see this right
now, but this is going to turn out to be
the best thing that ever happened to
you.
And now all these years later, it's
finally coming to pass.
John, in what way would you say you're a
you I mean, obviously
So in what way would you say
if I met you 15, 20 years ago,
how would I know what differences would
I notice between
the your personality then
[clears throat] and and your personality
now?
People have told me that I have I don't
see this in myself. I consider myself to
be a very happy, well-adjusted person.
People tell me, as recently as the day
before yesterday, that there's an
underlying sadness
that didn't exist before. I'm not really
sure exactly what they mean when they
say that, but I've gotten that from
several people independently of one
another.
Um
politically, Ted, I was way way more
mainstream. Okay.
You were like a You were like a Democrat
or what would you say?
>> I was a Democrat and a pretty sort of,
you know, down the line, well, you know,
this isn't my guy, but I'm a Democrat,
so I'm going to fall in line. Sure. But
that That Those days are gone. Gone.
I'll never ever do that again. You know,
I I've told the story in my first book
that
my grandfather, until the day he died,
um
had a framed picture of Franklin
Roosevelt on the top of the TV. When I
was a little kid, I thought that was a
relative of ours.
I still have that picture.
Oh, that's that's adorable. My
grandfather had one in his garage over
his workbench. See?
I still have it. I'm going to put it in
my office when I finally get an office.
Um but
you know, where Joe Biden certainly
wasn't mine. I mean, I I didn't vote for
Joe Biden anyway, but
um I I would have fallen into line 15
years ago.
And that just is never ever going to
happen again. Not unless,
you know, the McGovern people take over
the party again.
Yeah, that's not going to happen.
They're They're being fought tooth and
tongue, the far left.
>> It'll never ever happen, Scott. The
Democrats came up with the most
anti-democratic system that's ever
existed in American politics, and that's
the super delegate. Disgusting.
>> don't give a [__] who Democratic voters
vote for. The super delegates are going
to make the the choice. And you know
when that happened? When was McGovern in
'72? Because of McGovern. Well, no, it
was actually because of Humphrey in '68.
They were because McCarthy had won the
many of the primaries. He actually had
booted LBJ out of the race. Yeah. And
then they come to the convention and
they say, well, you know, Gene, thanks
thanks for everything, man. We're giving
it to Hubert. Yeah, you've done You've
done your part. Well, Well, I worked out
well. uproar
so much uproar in the DNC that they
decided that they're going to open the
primary system up. Just, you know,
really just let it run the way Oh, I
don't know, democracy should be run,
which is, you know, And so McGovern
People forget in '72 while the race was
between This is great history. It was
between McGovern
and George Wallace. Wallace had just won
the Florida primary, which was huge, and
was campaigning in Maryland when he was
shot. That's right.
>> Had that continued, could you imagine
what that convention would have been
like?
>> [laughter]
>> That would have split the party into
two. Yeah, well, it kind of did. And
McGovern gets the nomination. Um he
because he won the most votes. Yeah.
And the Democratic Party, the powers
that be, went back and said, holy [__]
we can't let that happen twice.
And that's why And that's how we got
Jimmy Carter. Um Mo Udall was in '76 was
one of the That's right.
Mo Udall was actually a terrific
candidate. I mean, he was terrific.
You know, I got to meet him in 1983
or four. I was I was the president of
the George Washington University College
Democrats. And we invited Mo Udall to
come and speak.
And he said, do you mind if I
if I
prepare a formal speech. We knew what he
was talking about. He was thinking of
running for president again in '84.
I want to I want to do a formal speech
just to get reactions. And we're like,
oh my god, he's going to announce his
candidacy. Wow. So he came and gave the
speech minus that last line, yes, I'm
running, no, I'm not running.
But the context was clear that he was
not running for president. And it was
just after that that he announced that
he had Parkinson's disease.
But uh he came with Cliff Robertson, the
Academy Award-winning actor.
>> Yeah, sure. and his wife Dina Merrill,
the Academy Award-winning actress. And
um
They just arrived in a taxi. And, you
know, came into the little theater that
held 250 people and we did this speech
and then we all went out to you remember
Hamburger Hamlet in Georgetown?
We all went to Hamburger Hamlet together
and had cheese steaks.
>> [laughter]
>> No, he was a great guy. I mean people in
Tucson still talk about how it was
terrific.
>> Really a decent a very decent human
being. My father we was a general
manager of a TV station in Madison,
Wisconsin when Wisconsin primary in '76
was that was that was the battleground.
That was when I was good.
That was a big one.
>> It was actually bigger in '80 between
Carter and Kennedy. That's when Carter
had to win Wisconsin so he leaked that
we were developing a stealth bomber.
And just barely beat Kennedy. That was
the B-2B or no that was the
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah. Like it was long
rumored but he came out and said yeah we
we need this to fight the Soviets and
then Kennedy lost the Wisconsin primary.
>> More DNC skullduggery too. They changed
they changed the the
the rules so that the so that the
delegates
were no longer they were originally they
you know going to be unbound. And so
that like if something happened like say
a hostage
like a hostage crisis let's say
or high inflation let's say
that would cause a change of
circumstances between the primaries and
the and the general or a convention that
they you know they have the flexibility
to choose someone who was a little more
palatable but you know the party is like
yeah we're not going to let Ted Kennedy
be the nominee.
Yeah Ted was a
Kennedy delegate by the way.
Well my father of just to finish the
story was a general manager of a TV
station Madison so all the candidates
trundled through and would you know give
my dad a few minutes in his office to
chat. Um he talked about George Wallace
just hated George Wallace he said he
just exudes
ugly anger.
Uh Jimmy Carter he said he wasn't really
there. He just was just but you know he
was a sort of fact just not there. Mo
Udall my dad a lifelong Republican uh
really thought the world of of Mo Udall
and actually said you know who he
reminds me of? He reminds me of Abraham
Lincoln. Wow.
Wow.
>> Um
um and I forget who else Frank Church
was running
um I'm trying to think
this is before Jerry Brown jumped in.
Yeah. Birch Bayh from Indiana Frank
Church
right Jimmy Carter
God everybody was running in '76. Yeah
Bill Mills ran for a minute.
Who did? Wilbur Mills
OH DID HE
>> [laughter]
>> I HAD TOTALLY FORGOTTEN. OH
[clears throat] MY God he did the strip
>> out of the reflecting pool at the the
title basin bombshell. Yeah. The title
basin bombshell.
We are the only three people on the
planet I pretty much who remember what
know what the hell we're talking about.
Yeah she was Wilbur Mills was head just
real quick for our listeners Wilbur
Mills was the chairman of the Ways and
Means Committee in the House and he had
his caught having an affair with a
stripper whose title was the title basin
bombshell.
>> [laughter]
>> Um yeah I know they'll And they called
her the Washington fringe benefit. He
hired her he hired her despite the fact
that she did she he hired her as a
secretary despite the fact that she
couldn't type and she later testified
[laughter] that she barely knew how to
answer the phone.
There isn't anything really wrong with
that.
Um looking for I mean
this has been great thank you by the
way. Real quick we need to touch on Cuba
because that was um your friends. I
listened to him on NPR because we don't
have a 24-hour news station here it's
all talk and the last thing I want to
hear when I wake up is like well you
know BECAUSE LIBERALS WANT TO EAT YOUR
DOGS. Um so I I suck it up and listen to
exactly I suck it up listen to NPR in
the morning Cuba seems to be in the
crosshairs now apparently before we
finish with Iraq.
Um you thoughts just
too many to mention or Ted and I were
talking about this couple of days ago. I
went to Cuba three years ago. I I'd
always wanted to go I always wanted to
see it with my own eyes and then I ended
up getting invited to Cuba
to participate in the international book
fair because my first two books were
translated into Spanish and then
included in the in the Cuban national
library. So I went it was kind of a big
deal. We got to meet the president of
Cuba and a bunch of different people.
Um there were several things that struck
me.
One was
I mentioned to Ted the other day
I'm not a big fan of squash. I'll eat it
if I have to right? But it's squash
squash squash three meals a day every
single day squash and finally I'm like
what's up with squash guys?
How much squash can one person eat?
And the waiter said to me
the American embargo includes food. So
we can only eat what we can grow.
And it's squash season buddy.
Yeah the American people don't know
that. I don't know that they would like
riot in the streets if they did.
I know they wouldn't but but they would
be a little bothered I think if they
knew that these sanctions mean no food
medical equipment
>> medical stuff. Yeah.
Another thing that struck me was
was the
overt friendliness of everybody just
randomly people in the marketplace or on
the street or
wherever
literally everybody in Cuba has a
relative in Florida.
They love the United States. They hate
our government but they love the United
States they'd love to come here they
would love it if we were friends and we
could trade and everybody would be
happy. They just don't understand this
blockade after all these years more than
65 years of total blockade. They don't
get it. We're pissing ourselves. Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> Any day now it's going to work. Yes. So
you know the the the comments from the
president the other day that Cuba will
be mine he said I can do whatever I
want. Mhm. That's like exactly the
opposite. Yeah I'm going to take it.
That's exactly the opposite of the
message we should be sending. Cuba's
Cuba's a failed state because we failed
it right? We forced it into failure.
Okay we win. Let's declare victory we
won. By the way I love that I love that
whole thing like oh you know I heard
Marco Rubio the other day saying you
know their economy sucks communism just
doesn't work. Yeah but we don't
>> don't really know if communism would
work do we right? I mean you've imposed
trade those sanctions for 60 years.
You know maybe if you stay out of the
way then we'd know if communism could
work.
Yeah.
>> So what do you what what do you suspect
what hijinks do you suppose suspect the
Trump administration to be launching
against Cuba if if they can get their
asses out of Iran which I'm not sure
that's a possibility. No yeah I agree
with you I think we're stuck there. I
think that this um
this embargo on fuel is is going to be
what does them in.
Because they were getting their gas or
their oil from Venezuela. Before that
they were getting it from the Russians
and then with the sanctions on the the
Russian oil and gas industry they
started getting it from Venezuela then
we overthrow the Venezuelan government
and grab Maduro.
Now I mean I'm sure you've seen the
footage there are literally no cars on
the road.
Everybody's either walking or bicycling.
That's it. So if anything
is going to push them over the edge I
think it's going to be that which is
funny to me because at the CIA we used
to say
all the time
that the policy was just wrong. The
embargo was wrong.
You want to overthrow the the
Cuban government?
Open a McDonald's.
When the first McDonald's opens that
whole government falls apart.
Encourage yeah I always used to say just
encourage tons of tourism
you know how lots of Americans just come
there and hang out and talk to people.
And they'll be like oh what's it like in
you know back in Miami? What's it like
in New York? Yeah. And they all know
because they all have relatives in New
York and Miami.
We've had a guest on the show who's
worked in you know liberating Cuba
politics for years Ricardo Aparicio
an attorney formerly with GE and he
still has friends and family down there
and the the story he's telling in the
last few weeks it's horrific. It's
absolutely horrific and they they lost
power I think What yesterday or just
And that kills that literally kills
people.
>> Yeah. Well people can't get to hospitals
they you know they can't breathing
machines stop working incubators stop
working.
Yeah.
People get stuck in elevators have heart
attacks whatever.
Before you mentioned your kids and I
just want to I want to come back to the
the internet fame stuff. How are the how
old are your kids and I'm not asking out
of the goodness Oh let's see they are 33
30 21 19 and 14. How are they handling
cuz it's not you have an unusual name
it's Greek and so everyone thinks my
name is Greek it's not it's Lithuanian
actually. Um I thought it was with with
the IS. Yeah that every name is so funny
to talk to Lithuanians cuz everyone has
that damn IS at the end of their name.
But how are your kids handling the fame?
I mean
are they getting any residual kickback
or are they do they think it's hilarious
that
Their friends are fascinated by it.
Fascinated.
>> I bet I bet. My kids my kids never cared
that I was a cartoonist their friends
thought it was awesome.
I mean they would they would just they
would just like trip over themselves you
know just oh a cartoonist that's so cool
and my kids are looking at me going that
[__] really cuz
>> [laughter]
>> you haven't seen watching the house
scratching his ass Like three three
weeks ago my niece called like 7:00 in
the morning
and she said Uncle John you're blowing
up on TikTok.
I said why?
And she goes I don't know.
And then it just she went crazy from
there.
So, do they care at all or do they just
pretty much like, nah, it's just a
>> they're they're like they're amused by
it.
A little bit perplexed.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah. No, they are. To tell you the
truth, Scott, I've been telling these
same stories for the last, you know,
what?
17 years. Well, that's the part. When I
was talking to
about this yesterday and I'm like,
I'm like, the guy got out of jail, got
out of prison 11 years ago, languishing
in obscurity,
um, you know, can can barely can't make
ends meet. And then and no one cares
about the story, right? No one cares
about the torture program, no one cares
about, you know, no one's ever been held
to account, nothing matters.
And then suddenly Tik Tok puts you on
the map. It's
I mean, it is idiocracy. It is, it's
crazy. But, you know what? These things
end as quickly as they begin. So, I'm
embracing it. It's going to be a load of
fun. And then when it goes away, I'll go
back to more serious things. Enjoy the
ride, for sure.
Oh, yeah, this is awesome. I mean, you
know, we talked about Psy from Gangnam
Style. He's still Psy. He'll always be
Psy. Exactly, he'll always be Psy.
There's a Wikipedia page, you can look
back on it from years from now and and
say that guy was somebody.
Yeah. Yeah, no, for sure.
Who wrote Who wrote your your, um,
Wikipedia page? Because someone wrote
mine and they got some things wrong and
I tried to edit it. Yeah.
>> And it says, well, and then, you know,
at the end of it it says, well, what
authority do you have or what's your
authority actually? I go, because it's,
you know, me and they said, no, you
can't no.
>> I I don't know who in the world wrote my
Wikipedia page, but there's like one
>> No, it's not. And there's one egregious
error
that that friends of mine have reached
out and said, hey, that
this Wikipedia thing, it says you were
convicted of espionage. I'm like,
[clears throat] what? I was never
convicted of espionage.
Um, John, you're famous enough now that
you could probably call Jimmy Wales and
have it fixed. Yeah, that's what I'll
do.
I I have I have two friends who are like
registered Wikipedia editors. So, I'm
going to I'm going to talk to them and
have them There you go.
Yeah, I mean, people can keep [__]
around with it. Yeah, there's a major
mistake in mine, too.
Um, John, thank you so much. I don't
want to keep you any longer than you
we asked. You have 88 cameos to get to.
That's right. It's true. 90, 92. Now,
holy [__] Four just in the last half
hour. Wow.
John, thank you so much. That's John
Kiriakou, CIA whistleblower and my
co-host on Deconstructed with Ted Rall
and John Kiriakou, which airs Monday
through Friday 9:00 a.m. Eastern Time on
YouTube and Rumble live and you'll also
see,
um, and you so we'll be back tomorrow
John and I will be back tomorrow
morning.
Uh, and you can of course stream it
anytime. As always, the DMZ America
podcast comes to you at 11:00 a.m.
Eastern Time every Thursday. Scott,
always a pleasure and thanks for joining
us. No thanks. Yeah, that was fun. What
a great guy. Yeah, he's great. I see, I
don't feel as bad that you're seeing
another podcast behind my back.
>> [laughter]
>> It's becoming a more of a poly
relationship.
>> [laughter]
>> It's all about the talking.
Not about the sex.
All right. [laughter]
How is the sex? I don't know. We'll talk
about it after. Yeah, we'll talk about
it afterwards. Bye, everyone. Thanks so
much for joining us. See you next week.